A Guide to the Papers of Charles Julian Bishko, 1930-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- IV: University of Virginia: Committee Assignments, Final Reports and Related Materials
  - B: Corcoran Department of History: History Courses Offered, Lectures, Outlines, Assignments, Gradebooks
    - Miscellaneous [Restricted] Material 1938-[1986], (5 folders) (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous [Restricted] Material 1956-1970, (8 folders) (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous [Restricted] Material [1968]-1975, (9 folders) (Box 34)